Mykeshia James Chicago IL 708-543-9025

mykeshiajames1112@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE: Ten years (plus) of substantial experience and outstanding skills in customer service. Excellent interpersonal skills, ability to work well with others, in both supervisory and support staff roles. I am also proficient with database programs including Oracle and Microsoft office (excel, outlook, PowerPoint, and word).

EDUCATION: Malcolm X College 2007-2010

WORK HISTORY:

11/2016- 04/2019 FINANCIAL EDUCATION SERVICES (FES) Chicago IL

Marketing and Customer Service Representative

- Handled 85-100 inbound calls and emails from customers to provide them with accurate product information.
- Scheduling and following up appointments with customers.
- Meeting deadlines to hit monthly sales quotas.
- Entered a heavy amount of data into database system, when walking customers through the application process.

04/2013-10/2016 HUB GROUP Chicago IL

Customer Service Representative and Claims assistant

- Handled inbound calls, chats, and email issues from customers to provide them with accurate information.
- Assist with Workers Compensation and work injuries.
- Assist with collection and preservation of required documents following accidents (driver files, logs, maintenance, etc.)
- Provided quality customer service and exceeded all quality assurance goals.
- Recommended process improvements and worked with management to resolve escalation calls.

09/2010-12/2012 - UNITED HEALTH GROUP Schaumburg IL

Intake Coordinator and Customer Service Representative

- Handled an average of 85-95 inbound calls.
- Worked closely with management solving all escalation calls and life threatening calls.
- Assisted patients with mental health and substance abuse benefits.
- Provided customer service to organization employees
- Reviewed daily logs and notes from case management to assure continuity of care provided to patients, used discretion and independent judgement in Handing patient and physician complaints.
- Provided patients with referrals and authorizations to see mental health clinicians, psychologist, and psychiatrist.

07/2007 - 10/2009 TCF Call Center Schiller Park IL

Customer Service Representative

Performed daily inbound or outbound calls regarding personal and business accounts.

- Provided customers with accurate account information.
- Reversed fees, updated customer information, and stop payments on checks.
- Excelled in providing quality customer service.

CUSTOMER SERVICE EXPERIENCE: I am energetic, reliable, and professional. I've been successful with answering incoming customer calls, utilizing company policies to solve customer issues and directing calls to the managerial team when necessary. My commitment is for customer satisfaction and an ability to make quick and accurate decisions.

COMPUTER SKILLS: Typing 40+ wpm, Microsoft Office, and Oracle.